[
  {"front": "Die Karriere, -n", "back": "career"},
  {"front": "Das (Schul-)Fach, Die Fächer", "back": "(school) subject"},
  {"front": "Die Note, -n", "back": "grade"},
  {"front": "Das Gymnasium, Gymnasien", "back": "grammar school"},
  {"front": "Das Abitur (Sg)", "back": "school-leaving exam"},
  {"front": "Die Klasse, -n", "back": "class"},
  {"front": "Der Abschluss, Die Abschlüsse", "back": "qualification"},
  {"front": "Die Prüfung, -en", "back": "exam"},
  {"front": "faul (adj)", "back": "lazy"},
  {"front": "fleißig (adj)", "back": "hardworking"},
  {"front": "intelligent (adj)", "back": "intelligent"},
  {"front": "dumm (adj)", "back": "stupid"},
  {"front": "schrecklich (adj)", "back": "terrible"},
  {"front": "Sich streiten (haben)", "back": "argue"},
  {"front": "Sich verbessern (haben)", "back": "improve oneself"},
  {"front": "Das Verhalten (Sg)", "back": "behavior"},
  {"front": "streng (adj)", "back": "strict"},
  {"front": "Der Wunsch, die Wünsche", "back": "wish"},
  {"front": "Der Plan, Die Pläne", "back": "plan"},
  {"front": "Der Friseur,-e", "back": "hairdresser"},
  {"front": "Die Friseurin, -nen", "back": "hairdresser (female)"},
  {"front": "Der/die Jugendliche, -n", "back": "young person"},
  {"front": "Der Schauspieler, -/", "back": "actor"},
  {"front": "Die Schauspielerin, -nen", "back": "actress"},
  {"front": "Dass", "back": "that"},
  {"front": "vorhin (adv)", "back": "earlier"},
  {"front": "mittler- (adj)", "back": "middle"},
  {"front": "Die Aktivität, -en", "back": "activity"},
  {"front": "Der Junge, -n", "back": "boy"},
  {"front": "Das System, -e", "back": "system"},
  {"front": "Die (Fach-) Hochschule, -n", "back": "university of applied sciences"},
  {"front": "Die Gesamtschule, -n", "back": "comprehensive school"},
  {"front": "Die Realschule, -n", "back": "secondary school"},
  {"front": "Die Hauptschule, -n", "back": "general school"},
  {"front": "Die Mittelschule, -n", "back": "middle school"},
  {"front": "Die Berufsschule, -n", "back": "vocational school"},
  {"front": "freiwillig (adj)", "back": "voluntary"},
  {"front": "Die Krippe, -n", "back": "nursery"},
  {"front": "Die Grundschule, -n", "back": "primary school"},
  {"front": "Der Mechatroniker, -/", "back": "mechatronics engineer"},
  {"front": "Die Mechatronikerin, -nen", "back": "mechatronics engineer (female)"},
  {"front": "Die Physik (Sg)", "back": "physics"},
  {"front": "Die Biologie (Sg)", "back": "biology"},
  {"front": "Die Chemie (Sg)", "back": "chemistry"},
  {"front": "Die Geografie (Sg)", "back": "geography"},
  {"front": "Die Kunst (Sg)", "back": "art"},
  {"front": "Die Geschichte (Sg)", "back": "history"},
  {"front": "Die Sozialkunde (Sg)", "back": "social studies"},
  {"front": "Hassen (haben)", "back": "hate"},
  {"front": "Die Gesellschaft (Sg)", "back": "society"},
  {"front": "Die Leistung, -en", "back": "achievement"},
  {"front": "Der Beginn (Sg)", "back": "beginning"},
  {"front": "All- (adj)", "back": "all"},
  {"front": "Die Stimme, -n", "back": "voice"},
  {"front": "notwendig (adj)", "back": "necessary"},
  {"front": "Der Auftrifft, -e", "back": "performance"},
  {"front": "Speichern (haben)", "back": "save (data)"},
  {"front": "Löschen (haben)", "back": "delete"},
  {"front": "Die Festplatte, -n", "back": "hard drive"},
  {"front": "Die Voraussetzung, -en", "back": "requirement"},
  {"front": "Die Politik (Sg)", "back": "politics"},
  {"front": "Die Wirtschaft (Sg)", "back": "economics"},
  {"front": "Die Kultur, -en", "back": "culture"},
  {"front": "Der Vortrag, die Vorträge", "back": "lecture"},
  {"front": "Sich bewerben (haben)", "back": "apply for a job"},
  {"front": "Präsentieren (haben)", "back": "present"},
  {"front": "Der Experte, -n", "back": "expert"},
  {"front": "Die Expertin, -nen", "back": "expert (female)"},
  {"front": "Der Erfolg, -e", "back": "success"},
  {"front": "Der Streit (Sg)", "back": "argument"},
  {"front": "Der Ärger (Sg)", "back": "anger"},
  {"front": "Lösen (haben)", "back": "solve"},
  {"front": "Teilnehmen (haben)", "back": "participate"},
  {"front": "Die Kündigung, -en", "back": "termination"},
  {"front": "Solch- (adj)", "back": "such"},
  {"front": "Sich fürchten (haben)", "back": "be afraid"},
  {"front": "Führen (haben)", "back": "lead"},
  {"front": "Das Klima (Sg)", "back": "climate"},
  {"front": "Die Technik (Sg)", "back": "technology"},
  {"front": "Sich verhalten (haben)", "back": "behave"},
  {"front": "Die Situation, -en", "back": "situation"},
  {"front": "Die Theorie, -n", "back": "theory"},
  {"front": "praktisch (adj)", "back": "practical"},
  {"front": "Der Verkehr (Sg)", "back": "traffic"},
  {"front": "Sich verletzen (haben)", "back": "injure oneself"},
  {"front": "Bluten (haben)", "back": "bleed"},
  {"front": "Der Notarzt, die Notärzte", "back": "emergency doctor"},
  {"front": "Der Traum, Die Träume", "back": "dream"},
  {"front": "unbedingt (adv)", "back": "absolutely"},
  {"front": "nebenbei (adv)", "back": "incidentally"},
  {"front": "Die Heimat (Sg)", "back": "homeland"},
  {"front": "sogenannt (adj)", "back": "so-called"},
  {"front": "Die Klinki, -en", "back": "clinic"},
  {"front": "vor allem (adv)", "back": "especially"},
  {"front": "Das Tier, -e", "back": "animal"},
  {"front": "Sammeln (haben)", "back": "collect"},
  {"front": "Der Rest, -e", "back": "rest"},
  {"front": "Bestehen (haben)", "back": "pass (exam)"},
  {"front": "Realisieren (haben)", "back": "realize"},
  {"front": "Entdecken (haben)", "back": "discover"},
  {"front": "Die Zukunft", "back": "future"},
  {"front": "Der Astronaut, -en", "back": "astronaut"},
  {"front": "Die Astronautin, -nen", "back": "astronaut (female)"}
]
